{
    "subject": "resource/Mura,_Barcelona",
    "predicate": "ontology/isPartOf",
    "object": "resource/Province_of_Barcelona",
    "human_readable": "Mura is part of Province of Barcelona.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8966536521911621,
            "question": "What province is Mura part of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6015715003013611,
            "question": "Where is Mura located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5702138543128967,
            "question": "Is Mura in Spain?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5393201112747192,
            "question": "What are some characteristics of the Province of Barcelona?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5169962644577026,
            "question": "Can you name a city within the Province of Barcelona?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4763062298297882,
            "question": "What is the capital of the Province of Barcelona?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44111621379852295,
            "question": "What are some popular tourist destinations within the Province of Barcelona?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2760859429836273,
            "question": "How diverse is the population in the Province of Barcelona?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16764774918556213,
            "question": "Are there any famous landmarks in Mura?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.0988508015871048,
            "question": "Does Mura have a rich history?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Mura is part of Province of Barcelona.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1823_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous landmarks in Mura?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1823_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How diverse is the population in the Province of Barcelona?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1823_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some popular tourist destinations within the Province of Barcelona?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1823_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1823_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1823_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1823_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1823_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1823_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1823_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1823_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1823_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1823_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1823_81.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON answer:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe context information provides multiple documents about the municipality of Mura, and in all of them, it is stated that Mura is a municipality in the province of Barcelona. This information supports the triple statement that Mura is part of the Province of Barcelona, confirming the answer as \"yes\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Mura is part of the Province of Barcelona.\" Each document consistently mentions that Mura is located in the province of Barcelona, autonomous community of Catalonia, Spain."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}